iphonephotographyschool.com 2015-12-13

# Privacy Policy

iPhonePhotographySchool.com is committed to ensuring your privacy is protected. This Privacy Policy, effective 30 June, 2015, sets out how the Site – iPhonePhotographySchool.com, owned by:

iPS Training LLC, uses and protects any information that you (“you” or “user”) provide us when you use the Site. If you have questions or comments regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us at [Emil@iPhonePhotographySchool.com](mailto:Emil@iPhonePhotographySchool.com).

## Information We Collect and How We Use It

To be able to use certain areas and features of the Site, specifically requested by you, we may require you to provide us with information that identifies you personally. This information may include:

  * Your name
  * Your email address
  * Billing address
  * Telephone number
  * Credit card/payment account information

The information we collect may be used to verify your identity, to correspond with you (such as through email newsletters or correspondence to us initiated by you), and to bill you for the service offered by the Site that you have subscribed to.

All email newsletters contain instructions to unsubscribe from the mailing list. You can also contact us at [Emil@iPhonePhotographySchool.com](mailto:Emil@iPhonePhotographySchool.com) to remove your email address from our mailing list at any time.

We will never sell or share your personal information to any person or organization except when required by law for the investigation of illegal or criminal activities, the exercise of legal rights or in defense against any legal claims, or otherwise.

## Your Credit Card Information

At the time of payment, your credit card information is passed securely using 128bit SSL to our payment gateway. We never store your credit card information for any reason.

## How We Ensure the Security of Your Information

iPhonePhotographySchool.com is committed to ensuring that your identifiable and non-identifiable personal information is secure. We have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to prevent unauthorized access, modification, disclosure, or loss of your identifiable personal information. However, we cannot assure your identifiable and non-identifiable personal information will never be disclosed in a nature that conflicts with this Privacy Policy. Additionally, we are not responsible for any breach of security or actions undertaken by any third party that receive the information.

## Cookies – How We Use Them

A cookie is a small file sent to your browser from a Web server to be stored on your computer. A cookie cannot give access to your computer or any information stored on your computer. We use cookies to allow the Site to respond to you as an individual by gathering and remembering information about your preferences when using the Site so when you next visit the Site your preferences are already set. Cookies are also used to personalize the content you view on the Site (such as your Update Feed). You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website. To view more information regarding cookie settings please visit:

For Microsoft Internet Explorer: <http://www.microsoft.com/info/cookies.mspx>

For Google Chrome: <http://www.google.com/support/chrome/bin/answer.py?answer=95647>

For Mozilla Firefox: <http://support.mozilla.com/en-US/kb/Enabling%20and%20disabling%20cookies>

For Apple Safari 8: [https://support.apple.com/kb/PH19214?viewlocale=en_US&locale=en_US](https://support.apple.com/kb/PH19214?viewlocale=en_US&locale=en_US)

## Online Advertising We Use

We use Google ADWORDS Remarketing to advertise iPhonePhotographySchool.com across the Internet. ADWORDS Remarketing will display relevant ads tailored to you based on what parts of the iPhonePhotographySchool.com website you have viewed by placing a cookie on your machine. THIS COOKIE DOES NOT IN ANY WAY IDENTIFY YOU OR GIVE ACCESS TO YOUR COMPUTER. The cookie is used to say “This person visited this page, so show them ads relating to that page.” Google AdWords Remarketing allows us to tailor our marketing to better suit your needs and only display ads that are relevant to you.

## How to Opt Out of Remarketing and Advertising

If you do not wish to participate in our GOOGLE ADWORDS Remarketing, you can opt out by visiting Google’s Ads Preferences Manager.

You can also opt out of any third-party vendor’s use of cookies by visiting www.networkadvertising.org/choices/

## Controlling Your Personal Information

We make every effort to give you access to your personal information, to allow you to correct any inaccuracies, or to remove your personal information at your request provided it is not required for genuine business purposes or by law to be retained.

We require you identify yourself and the information you request to access, remove, modify or correct before commencing such requests. We may refuse requests that are of unreasonable technical effort or would be highly unfeasible, endanger the privacy of others, or require access that is not normally necessary. When we provide access to your personal information for the purposes of modification, correction or removal, we do so free of charge except where doing so requires an unreasonable effort.

To request access, correction or removal of your personal information, please contact [Emil@iPhonePhotographySchool.com](mailto:Emil@iPhonePhotographySchool.com). To request the removal of your account, please contact [Emil@iPhonePhotographySchool.com](mailto:Emil@iPhonePhotographySchool.com). We will remove all of your information and data from the Site within 7 business days upon receipt of your request.

## Updates and Changes to this Privacy Policy

Occasionally, we may change this Privacy Policy. Should we do so, we will post a notification on the Site. Changes will take effect from the date they are posted.
